<sburb>
   <classes>
       <action class='daveTalk' sprite='dave' command='talk'>
         <args>
         @dave_talk DAVE: blogging on the go karkat?
         @karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU JUST HAD TO FUCKING GO THIS WAY DIDN'T YOU?
         @dave_talk DAVE: probably not but here i am either way
         @dave_talk DAVE: so where you off to mr sunshine?
         @karkat_yell KARKAT: ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME THAT DAVE FUCKING STRIDER, ALMIGHTY PAJAMA-WEARING NOBLE KNIGHT OF DOUCHEBAGGERY...
         @karkat_talk KARKAT: ACTUALLY CARES TO ASK WHERE I'M GOING?
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe i dont
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe im just trying to make small talk
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe im only talking to avoid nose-diving into an awkward silence with you while you glance over at me randomly like youre trying to catch a sneak peek through the opaque sexual tension cloud that i just kind of assume is always surrounding you no matter who youre actually talking to
             
             @karkat_facepalm ...
             @karkat_talk KARKAT: I'M GOING UP TO THE OBSERVATION DECK.
             
             @dave_talk DAVE: oh then we are going the same way
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: did terezi ask you to too
             
             @karkat_talk KARKAT: I WAS GOING TO AVOID SAYING THAT ON A RECORDING BUT…
             @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: YES.
             
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: why dont you just stop recording or edit it out
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: come to think of it why dont all of us just do that when we say embarrasing shit
             @dave_talk DAVE: but seriously why dont you just deal with it later?
             @dave_talk DAVE: that shits got to be simple even for you
             
             @! A voice reverberates through the halls from an intercom speaker nearby.
             @! #0082824TT3NT1ON THR3SH3CUT1ON3R CH3RRYB3RRY 4ND MR C4NDYSP1C3!##
             @! #008282YOUR 1MM3D14T3 PR3S3NC3 1S R3QU1R3D ON TH3 OBS3RV4T1ON D3CK!##
             @! #008282F41LUR3 TO COMPLY W1TH TH3 4LM1GHTY COURTBLOCK’S 1NSTRUCT1ONS W1LL R3SULT 1N SW1FT 4ND D1R3 CONS3QU3NC3S FOR YOU BOTH!##
             @!:#notreally Oh man, this shit sounds serious.

         @karkat_shout KARKAT: HOLY TAINTCHAFING FUCK HAVE SOME FUCKING PATIENCE!
         @karkat_shout KARKAT: AND STOP WITH THE PET NAMES!
         @dave_huh DAVE: dude you know she cant hear you right
         @karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT? AM I NOT ALLOWED TO JUST FUCKING RAGE TO MYSELF?
         @dave_talk DAVE: its not really "to yourself" if i can hear it now is it?
         @! He stays close behind you as you continue on...
         <!--  -->
         </args>
      </action>
       
       <action class='roomEntrance' command='talk'>
           <args>
               @! Oh god. You remember this room... Something seems odd about it.
               @! It might be the fact that you just walked through a wall to get here.
               @! It might be that guy standing over there.
               @! Is that... is that Sollux? With EYES???
               @! You know what this means.
               @! You are now beyond the grips of canon interraction. Welcome to the fanon in-joke room. Enjoy your stay.
               </args>
           </action>
       
       
       <action class='solluxTalk' command='talk'>
           <args>
               @sollux_talk hey kk, fancy 2eeiing you here.
               @sollux_talk come back for more?
               @karkat_talk WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
               @sollux_talk ju2t waiit for iit, were iin the fanon room now. youll adju2t.
               @karkat_talk WHAT EXACTLY AM I ADJUSTING TO?
               @sollux_talk liike ii 2aiid, ju2t waiit and youll 2ync up.
               @karkat_talk I'M NOT SURE IF-
               @karkat_horror OH...
               @karkat_horror OH GOD WHERE DID THESE MEMORIES COME FROM?
               @karkat_shout OH GOD I'M ENJOYING SOME OF THEM, GET THEM OUT GET THEM OUT!
               @sollux_smug ehehehehe.
               @! Shortly thereafter they proceeded to fornicate.
               @! And there was much rejoicing.
           </args>
       </action>
       
       
       <action class='computer1' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! This looks familiar...
               @! wrigglerbase, hemoglobin, hemogoblin (avoiid at all co2t2), redgrub, nubhub (ha2 omorashi 2tuff)...
               @! This is from that one time sollux asked you if you knew any porn sites that were easy to get to.
               @! What the fuck does omorashi mean?
               @! Probably best you leave that unanswered.
           </args>
        </action>
       
       <action class='computer2' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! There appear to be some lyrics written on this one.
               @! WHEN I WAS A YOUNG GRUB...
               @! I'D ALWAYS IMAGINED THAT I'D GROW UP-
               @! You've heard these before.
           </args>
       </action>
       
       <action class='computer3' command="talk">
           <args>
               @! More lyrics on this one, it looks like.
               @! Some indie shit about people who try too hard.
               @! Pass.
           </args>
       </action>
       
       
       <action class='computer4' command='talk'>
           <args>
               @! There is an IM conversation open...
            @!~gameplan
               @! ANDREW: if you don't want there to be a loading time inbetween lowaa happening, just put it on the same image as the roof.
               @! CASE: I wouldn't mind a loading time really
               @! ANDREW: also what are the little red arrows?
               @! CASE: the red arrows are the opposing team attacking the linebacker
               @! CASE: obvs
               @! ANDREW: oh. how ever did i miss that.
               @! ANDREW: this is some a+ strategy you got going on there.  we're sure to win in the playoffs with your brilliance on our side.
               @! Dumb.
               
            </args>
        </action>

       
   </classes>
</sburb>
