<sburb description="lowaa">

  <dependencies>

    <dependency>karkat.xml</dependency>
    <dependency>tavros.xml</dependency>
    <dependency>eridan.xml</dependency>
    <dependency>lab1.xml</dependency>
    
  </dependencies>

  <assets>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_0_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_0_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_1_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_1_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_2_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_2_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_3_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_3_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_BG_4_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_BG_4_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_FG_0_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_0_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_0_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_0_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_0_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_0_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_0_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_0_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_FG_1_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_1_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_1_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_1_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_1_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_1_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_1_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_1_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_FG_2_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_2_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_2_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_2_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_2_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_2_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_2_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_2_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_3_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_3_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_3_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_3_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_3_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_3_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_3_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_3_3.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_4_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_4_0.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_4_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_4_1.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_4_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_4_2.png</asset>
        <asset name='lowaa_FG_4_3' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/lowaa_FG_4_3.png</asset>

        <asset name='lowaa_WM' type='graphic'>backgrounds/lowaa_WM.png</asset> 

        <asset name='lance' type='graphic'>objects/items/i_lance.png</asset>
        <asset name='ahab' type='graphic'>objects/items/i_ahab.png</asset>


  </assets>

  <sprite depthing='3' name='lance'>
        <animation sheet='lance'/>
    </sprite>

    <sprite depthing='3' name='ahab'>
        <animation sheet='ahab'/>
    </sprite>

  <rooms>
    <room name='lowaa' width='2100' height='1502' walkableMap='lowaa_WM'>

        <triggers>
            <trigger>spriteProperty,eridan,x&lt;1100
                    <trigger detonate='true'>spriteProperty,eridan,y&lt;450
                        <action command='removeSprite'>
                            <args>dave,lowaa</args>
                        </action>
                    </trigger>
                </trigger>

                <trigger>spriteProperty,eridan,x&lt;1100
                    <trigger detonate='true'>spriteProperty,eridan,y&lt;400
                        <action command='talk' noDelay='true'>
                            <args>
                                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: wwhat wwas up back there wwith aquablood?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: DO YOU REALIZE HOW EMBARASSING YOU ARE?
                
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhat?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU’VE BEEN DEAD FOR I DON’T KNOW HOW LONG, A FUCKING SWEEP MAYBE, AND YOU JUST START ACTING LIKE WE’RE BEST FRIENDS OR SOMETHING.
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: FIRST OFF, IT’S KIND OF...
                @karkat_sullen KARKAT: TRAUMATIZING?
                @karkat_sullen KARKAT: TO SEE SOMEONE TALKING TO ME HERE AND NOW WHEN I’VE SEEN THEIR MUTILATED CORPSE UP CLOSE BEFORE.
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: SECONDLY-
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: mutilated??
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: howw wwas i killed in your timeline
                
                @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: ...
                @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: KANAYA SAWED YOU IN HALF...
                
                @eridan_growl ERIDAN: that jadeblooded bitch
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: i knoww i might a annoyed her with the ashen requests but she didn’t have to-
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: WOW, ARE YOU REALLY THAT FUCKING SHALLOW THAT YOU THINK SOMEONE ELSE WOULD KILL YOU OVER SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU WERE PRETTY FUCKING INSANE, YOU KNOW. YOU TRIED TO KILL HER BY BLASTING A HOLE THROUGH HER CHEST WITH SOME BEEFED UP MAGIC WAND. AND ON TOP OF THAT-
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: magic wwand kar really
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: i must a been pretty fuckin stupid in your timeline too
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: since wwhen wwould i try to use magic for anythin
                
                @karkat_horror KARKAT: I
                @karkat_what KARKAT: ...
                @karkat_sullen KARKAT: ...
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: NO COMMENT.
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: BY THE WAY, IS THERE ANYONE IN THIS THING OTHER THAN YOU?
                
                @eridan_talk Eridan: wwell not right noww
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: but i havve run into others a feww times before
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: its not really anythin special usually
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: i still get pretty lonely out here
                @eridan_lip ERIDAN: vvery lonely an vvery cold
                @eridan_lip ERIDAN: i didnt evven know ghosts could feel cold
                @eridan_lip ERIDAN: youre lucky you at least havve people to interract with
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: 
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: hey kar
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhats that thing youre holding
                
                @karkat_what KARKAT: OH THIS
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: OH FUCK I NEVER STOPPED RECORDING DID I?
                @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: AGH...
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WELL AT LEAST THIS CAN PROVIDE SOME INSIGHT ON HOW MUCH IDIOTIC AND SPORADIC BULLSHIT I HAVE TO PUT UP  WITH BETWEEN RECORDING THINGS.
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: recordin wwhat 
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: IGNORE IT.
                
                @! You hear footsteps and decide to see if anyone else could be around, with Eridan tagging along.
                            </args>
                            <action command='moveSprite'> 
                                <args>tavros,1680,1020</args>
                                
                            </action>
                        </action>
                    </trigger>
                </trigger>

                <trigger>spriteProperty,tavros,x&lt;1800
                    <trigger>spriteProperty,eridan,y&gt;970
                        <trigger detonate = 'true'> spriteProperty,eridan,x&gt;1510
                            <action command='talk' noDelay='true'>
                                <args>
                                    @tavros_blink TAVROS: hEY,,,

                    @karkat_horror KARKAT: FUCK!
                    
                    @karkat_yell KARKAT: TAVROS WHERE THE FUCK DID YOU COME FROM?
                    
                    @tavros_talk TAVROS: i,,, tHINK MY BUBBLE MUST HAVE SWEPT THROUGH THIS ONE,,,
                    
                    @tavros_blink TAVROS: aND, nOW I’M HERE I GUESS,
                    
                    @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: THIS IS THE DUMBEST FUCKING CLUSTERFUCK REUNION EVER.
                    
                    @karkat_what KARKAT: WAIT TAVROS, WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOUR PANTS?
                    
                    @eridan_huh ERIDAN: yeah wwhat the hell kind of getup is that dirtblood
                    @eridan_talk ERIDAN: that looks so ridiculous
                    
                    @tavros_talk TAVROS: oH, iT’S MY GOD TIER OUTFIT,
                    @tavros_talk2 TAVROS: wHEN I GOT TO IT I GOT LEGS AGAIN, aND I GUESS THE GAME WANTED ME TO NOTICE OR SOMETHING,
                    @tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: pANTS WOULD BE, nICE THOUGH,
                    
                    @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: I’M SORRY BUT I CAN’T EVEN LOOK AT YOU, YOU’RE JUST EMBARRASSING.
                    
                    @tavros_sadtalk TAVROS: yEAH, i KNOW,
                    
                    @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: THIS JUST KEEPS GETTING MORE AND MORE AWKWARD.
                    
                    @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: I’LL JUST CATCH THE NEXT DEAD ERIDAN THAT DRIFTS BY, I’M GOING BACK DOWNSTAIRS.
                    
                    @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: no kar
                    @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: you don’t havve to be like that
                    
                    @karkat_talk KARKAT: YES I DO.
                    @karkat_yell KARKAT: WATCH ME, MAGICALLY BECOME ABSENT FROM THIS SHITTY DREAM PLANET WITH PANTLESS DEAD FRIENDS. LATER, FUCKERS!
                    @! You storm out, leaving your parallel dead friends in their bubble.
                </args>
                                <action command='unfollow'>
                                    <args>eridan</args>
                                    <action command='setGameState'>
                                        <args>leaveLOWAA,true</args>
                                        <action command='changeRoomRemote'>
                                            <args>lab1.xml,lab1,1690,3035</args>
                                            <action command='walk'>
                                                <args>char,Left</args>
                                                <action command='talk'>
                                                    <args>
                                                        @! Well, that nightmare of a bubble is over.
                                                        @! The place seems quiet. Maybe you could get back to alchemizing stuff. Or not. Maybe you could just wander around. What else is there to do? Awful lot of meteor to explore.
                                                    </args>
                                                </action>
                                            </action>
                                        </action>
                                    </action>
                                </action>
                            </action>
                        </trigger>
                    </trigger>
                </trigger>

        </triggers>
  

      <character name='karkat' x='980' y='490' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='karkatSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
      </character>

      <character name='tavros' x='2000' y='50' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='tavrosSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
      </character>

      <character name='dave' x='918' y='841' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='daveSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
        <action command='talk' name='Talk to Dave.'>
                    <args>
                        @dave_smug DAVE: so who the fuck’s memories are these? im kind of digging the set 
                        @dave_talk DAVE: im gettin this hunchback of notre dame vibe except for gargoyles that come to life and completely ruin the movie its a bunch of weird black winged monster things.
                        @dave_concern DAVE: hey have we been here before?
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: ACTUALLY WE HAVE. IT’S WHERE THE MAYOR WAS REVIVED.
                        @dave_talk DAVE: ah right cool
                        @dave_talk DAVE: for real though
                        @dave_smug DAVE: these palaces or whatever are some legitimately class shit here
                        @dave_smug DAVE: like some “i feel like i should be waiting for a science professor to show up” level of class
                        @karkat_horror KARKAT: DON’T SAY THAT WORD TOO LOUD!
                        @karkat_yell KARKAT: IT COULD BE A FUCKING DUCK CALL AROUND HERE, YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
                        @dave_huh DAVE: what class
                        @karkat_shout KARKAT: NO, YOU IDIOT-
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i’m certainly no professor but i do knoww quite a bit about science
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: is there currently a discussion going on
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i wwouldn’t mind joining in
                        @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: TOO LATE...
                        @dave_smug DAVE: oh yeah this douchebag
                        @dave_talk DAVE: hey weren’t you dressed like psyduck before 
                        @dave_concern DAVE: shit you probably dont remember do you
                        @dave_huhtalk DAVE: damn that wasn’t even technically you
                        @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i just confused myself there
                        @dave_mad DAVE: doomed timelines are stupid
                        @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: (like he'd even know what a fucking psyduck is...)
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwait
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwho...
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: wwhat the hell kind of creature is that
                        @dave_smug DAVE: oh right you assholes couldnt even all stay alive before you actually met any of us could you
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: YEAH, HE PROBABLY DIED BEFORE SGRUB ENDED.
                        @dave_concern DAVE: alright then I got this
                        @dave_smug DAVE: greetings dead alternate timeline alien whose name i dont care about i am dave s obana and i will be your ambassador to my species
                        @dave_smug DAVE: the pajama draped musclebreasted hollering phallus baboon
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: pajama wwhat
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: hollerin wwhat
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: kar is this guy for real
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: HE’S A HUMAN, HE’S...
                        @karkat_what KARKAT: IT’S...
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S NOT IMPORTANT, JUST IGNORE HIM.
                        @dave_madtalk DAVE: dont try to undermine the importance of this inter-realm ambassadorship
                        @dave_madtalk DAVE: before you know it shits gonna go haywire and the afterlife is gonna explode or implode or crack apart or something and how are we gonna know about it? 
                        @dave_talk DAVE: gotta keep our shit tight with these white eyed folk
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: I COULD SIT HERE AND KEEP TELLING YOU HOW MUCH MORE IDIOTIC YOU KEEP SOUNDING, BUT YOU’D COME RIGHT BACK WITH EVEN MORE STUPID IRONIC RAMBLING AND I WOULD STILL THINK THE SAME THING BUT EVEN WORSE, AND IT WOULD BE A NO WIN SITUATION. 
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: SO I THINK WHAT I’M GOING TO DO IS WALK AWAY NOW, TO MAKE SURE I DON’T SPARK ANY MORE OF YOUR TIRED AND SARCASTIC VERBAL ESSAYS ON IRRELEVANCE.
                        @dave_smug DAVE: suit yourself nubs
                    </args>
                    <action command='removeAction' >
                        <args>dave,Talk to Dave.</args>
                       <action command='moveSprite'> 
                            <args>eridan,980,790</args>
                            <action command='removeAction'>
                                <args>terezi,Talk to Terezi.</args>
                                <action command='addAction'>
                                    <args>terezi,
                                        <action command='talk' name='Talk to Terezi.'>
                                            <args>
                                                @terezi_talk TEREZI: HOW K1ND OF YOU TO JO1N US DOOM3D D34D 3R1D4N!
                
                @terezi_talk TEREZI: 1 4M RUNN1NG SHORT ON M3MB3RS OF TH3 JURY, 4ND 4T TH3 R4T3 W3 4R3 GO1NG W3 4R3 1N D4NG3R OF N3V3R C4TCH1NG D3T3CT1V3 DULC3’S MURD3R3R!
                
                @terezi_talk TEREZI: 1 4M 4FR41D TH4T 1 W1LL SOON N33D TO BYP4SS TH3 CURR3NT D1SCUSS1ON 1N ORD3R TO D1SP3NS3 SOM3...
                
                @terezi_laugh TEREZI: H34V13R 1NT3RROG4T1ON M3THODS!
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: despite this afterlife thing bein a wwhole eternity-long deal
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: i dont havve time for your outlandish make-believe court dramas
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: hey kar while they’re busy RPing and stuff how about I show you around my planet
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: i remember most of the cool parts so it should all be here
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: maybe wwe could finally catch up for real
                
                @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS A LOT MORE EXCITING THAN LISTENING TO FAKE JUDICIAL BABBLE...
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 4M GROW1NG QU1T3 1MP4T13NT 4ND 4NGRY!
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 4M W4RN1NG YOU, DO NOT CROSS TH3 COURTBLOCK MR THR3SH3CUT1ON3R!
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: REALLY, TEREZI, YOU KEPT ANNOYING DAVE AND I INTO COMING UP HERE TODAY, AND THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST LACKLUSTER INCENTIVES YOU COULD HAVE GIVEN US TO DO SO.
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: AND SERIOUSLY, WE’RE NOT EVEN IN A COURT, WE’RE IN THE LAND OF WRATH AND ANGELS.
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: EXCEPT WE’RE NOT EVEN IN THE LAND OF WRATH AND ANGELS WE’RE ON THE FUCKING ROOF OF A BUILDING ON THIS FUCK FORSAKEN ASTEROID.
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU COULD TRY TO CONSIDER THAT POSSIBLY I’D LIKE TO TALK TO A NON-HOMOCIDAL AND NON-SHITHIVE MAGGOTS VERSION OF ONE OF MY OLD FRIENDS INSTEAD OF CATERING TO YOUR FUCKED UP JUDGEMURDER ROLEPLAY NEEDS?
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: >://
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: YOU KNOW WH4T?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 4T TH1S PO1NT YOU C4N 4LL DO WH4T3V3R TH3 FUCK YOU W4NT
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: ARE YOU SERIOUSLY MAD THAT WE DIDN’T WANT TO BE FORCED INTO ROLEPLAYING?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT DID YOU EVEN WANT TO DO THIS FOR?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: WHY SHOULD YOU C4R3?
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WELL IF YOU WANTED TO DO SOMETHING YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST PLANNED IT BETTER.
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: OR GIVEN US NOTICE.
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WE’RE NOT REALLY THE FUCKING ECCENTRIC ROLEPLAYING TYPE LIKE YOU ARE.
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: WH4T3V3R
                
                @karkat_what KARKAT: ...
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WELL SORRY.
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: you tell her kar
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: don’t let some blind psychopath and her pretend games get betwween us
                
                @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: ERIDAN OF THE AMOUNT OF WORD COMBINATIONS YOU COULD FORCE OUT OF YOUR CHITINOUS WINDTUBE THAT WAS POSSIBLY THE WORST POSSIBLE THING.
                
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhat
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: i just meant-
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: AND WHAT DO YOU MEAN, BETWEEN US?
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: DUDE, WE WERE NEVER EVEN _THAT_ CLOSE, OK?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: I DON’T WANT TO GET INTO A FUCKING SPLIT DIMENSION ANTICONFESSION EMOTIONAL BULLSHITCIRCUS, SO CAN YOU JUST NOT SOUND SO STRANGELY ATTATCHED FOR ONCE?
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: ESPECIALY IN FRONT OF OTHER PEOPLE?
                
                @dave_concern DAVE: what the fuck is even happening over there
                @dave_huhtalk DAVE: of all the awkward things thats happened on this asteroid
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: CAN YOU BLUBBERING COCKHEADS JUST CAN IT FOR A SECOND? I’M TRYING TO GET A MESSAGE ACROSS HERE!
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: K4RK4T 1 R3GR3T TO 1NFORM YOU TH4T TH3 ONLY “BLUBB3R1NG COCKH34D” 1N TH3 1MM3D14T3 V1C1N1TY 1S YOU
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: SWEET SLUDGESPEWING FUCK WHY AM I THE FUCKING BAD GUY HERE?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 DON’T KNOW BUT S1NC3 4PP4R3NTLY 1’M NOT 1NT3R3ST1NG 3NOUGH, 1 TH1NK 1’LL JUST GO.
                
                @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: TEREZI, COME ON...
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: NO
            </args>
            <action command='removeSprite'>
                <args>terezi,lowaa</args>
            </action>
        </action>
    </args>
</action>
                        </action>
                    </action>
                </action>
                </action>
      </character>

      <character name='terezi' x='869' y='771' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='tereziSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
        <action command='talk' name='Talk to Terezi.'>
                    <args>
                    @karkat_talk KARKAT: I GUESS YOUR ROLEPLAY PLANS CAN’T REALLY GO THROUGH NOW, HUH?
                    @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: DR34MBUBBL3S NOTW1THST4ND1NG M4Y 1 R3M1ND YOU BOTH TH4T W3 4R3 ST1LL 1N TH3 M1DDL3 OF 4N 1MPORT4NT 1NT3RV13W!
                    @terezi_talk TEREZI: NOW CH3RRYB3RRY COULD YOU PL34S3 D3SCR1B3 TH3-
                    @karkat_talk KARKAT: I’D RATHER NOT.
                    @terezi_mad TEREZI: >://
                    @karkat_talk KARKAT: SORRY.
                    @terezi_mad TEREZI: >://
                    </args>
                </action>
      </character>

      <character name='eridan' x='2000' y='50' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='eridanSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
        <action command='talk' name='Talk to Eridan.'>
                    <args>
                    @eridan_huh ERIDAN: so kar are you all alivve
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: like actually alivve
                        @karkat_what KARKAT: YEAH...
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: wwhat a fuckin relief for once
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: all the other bubbles i cross through wwent through timelines so different
                        @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: and they all don’t remember jack shit about wwhat happened
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S THE SAME WITH THE FEW VERSIONS OF YOU THAT I’VE MET. I DOUBT WE WENT THROUGH ANY OF THE SAME FUCKING STUFF YOU DID.
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: i don’t knoww
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i guess it just feels more genuine or something
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: you look older though
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: WE’VE BEEN OUT HERE FOR OVER HALF A SWEEP.
                        @karkat_what KARKAT: I THINK THAT’S ABOUT A YEAR AND A FEW MONTHS IN HUMAN TIME.
                        @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhats a human
                        @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: UGH...
                        @karkat_yell KARKAT: THESE PALE MOTHERFUCKERS LIKE THE GUY IN THE RED GEAR PAJAMAS.
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: are they game constructs or
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: NO, THEY’RE FROM A DIFFERENT UNIVERSE.
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: THE ONE WE FUCKING CREATED WHEN WE WON THE GAME.
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: BUT THROUGH A COMBINATION OF ME FUCKING UP AND THEM FUCKING UP...
                        @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: WE NEVER REALLY FULLY WON.
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: SO WE’VE BEEN WORKING WITH THEM ON CHEATING THE SYSTEM.
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: IT’S A LONG AND INCREDIBLY CONVOLUTED STORY THAT WOULD PROBABLY TAKE NEARLY 2 SWEEPS AND EIGHT THOUSAND PAGES TO TELL ACCURATELY.
                        @eridan_talk ERIDAN: i think i get it
                        @karkat_talk KARKAT: GOOD, BECAUSE I DON’T.
                        @! You start to wonder if Terezi’s noticed Eridan’s arrival. If anything is going to interrupt her RP streak, this will.
                    </args>
                    <action command='follow'>
                        <args>eridan,char</args>
                        <action command='removeAction'>
                            <args>eridan,Talk to Eridan.</args>
                        </action>
                    </action>
                </action>
      </character>
  


      <sprite name='lowaa_BG'>
                <animation sheet='lowaa_BG' sliced='true' numCols='5' numRows='4' colSize='500' rowSize='500'/>
            </sprite>

            <sprite name='lowaa_FG' depthing='2'>
                <animation sheet='lowaa_FG' sliced='true' numCols='5' numRows='4' colSize='500' rowSize='500'/>
            </sprite>

    </room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>
 

