<sburb>
   <classes>
      <action class='daveInterrupt' name='talk to dave' command='talk'>
         <args>
         @dave_talk DAVE: blogging on the go karkat?
         @karkat_talk KARKAT: YOU JUST HAD TO FUCKING GO THIS WAY DIDN'T YOU?
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe im not
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe im just trying to make small talk
         @dave_smug DAVE: maybe im talking to avoid nose-diving into an awkward silence with you while you glance over at me randomly like youre trying to catch a sneak peek through the opaque sexual tension cloud that i just kind of assume is always surrounding you no matter who youre actually talking to
             
             @karkat_facepalm ...
             @karkat_talk KARKAT: I'M GOING UP TO THE OBSERVATION DECK.
             
             @dave_talk DAVE: oh then we are going the same way
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: did terezi ask you to too
             
             @karkat_talk KARKAT: I WAS GOING TO AVOID SAYING THAT ON A RECORDING BUT…
             @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: YES.
             
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: why dont you just stop recording or edit it out
             @dave_huhtalk DAVE: come to think of it why dont all of us just do that when we say embarrasing shit
             @dave_talk DAVE: but seriously why dont you just deal with it later? \nthat shits got to be simple even for you
             
             @karkat_talk: THERE'S PROBABLY SOME WEIRD PSYCHOLOGICAL REASON FOR THAT BUT-
             @! A voice reverberates through the halls from an intercom speaker nearby.
             @! #008282 4TT3NT1ON THR3SH3CUT1ON3R CH3RRYB3RRY 4ND MR C4NDYSP1C3 YOUR 1MM3D14T3 PR3S3NC3 1S R3QU1R3D ON TH3 OBS3RV4T1ON D3CK!##
             @! #008282 F41LUR3 TO COMPLY W1TH TH3 4LM1GHTY COURTBLOCK’S 1NSTRUCT1ONS W1LL R3SULT 1N SW1FT 4ND D1R3 CONS3QU3NC3S FOR YOU BOTH!##
             @!:#notreally Oh man, this shit sounds serious.

         @karkat_shout KARKAT: HOLY TAINTCHAFING FUCK HAVE SOME FUCKING PATIENCE!
         @karkat_shout KARKAT: AND STOP WITH THE PET NAMES!
         @dave_huh DAVE: dude you know she cant hear you right
         @karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT? AM I NOT ALLOWED TO JUST FUCKING RAGE TO MYSELF?
         @dave_talk DAVE: its not really "to yourself" if i can hear it now is it?
         <!--  -->
         </args>
      </action>
   </classes>
</sburb>
