<sburb description='terezi'>
    <dependencies>
        </dependencies>
    
    <classes>
        <animation class='terezi-dialog' frameInterval='6' x='-180' y='-454'/>
        
        <character class='terezi' name='terezi' x='287' y='330' sx='-37' sy='-65' sWidth='75' sHeight='75' width='36' height='16' sheet='tereziSheet' state='walkFront' facing='Front'>
        </character>
        
        <action class='tereziTalk3' name='Talk to Terezi.' command='talk'>
            <args>
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: I GUESS YOUR ROLEPLAY PLANS CAN’T REALLY GO THROUGH NOW, HUH?

                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: DR34MBUBBL3S NOTW1THST4ND1NG M4Y 1 R3M1ND YOU BOTH TH4T W3 4R3 ST1LL 1N TH3 M1DDL3 OF 4N 1MPORT4NT 1NT3RV13W!

                @terezi_talk TEREZI: NOW CH3RRYB3RRY COULD YOU PL34S3 D3SCR1B3 TH3-

                @karkat_talk KARKAT: I’D RATHER NOT.

                @terezi_mad TEREZI: >:/

                @karkat_talk KARKAT: SORRY.

                @terezi_mad TEREZI: >:/
             </args>
         </action>
        
        
        <action class='tereziTalk4' name='Talk to Terezi' command='talk'>
            <args>  
                @terezi_talk TEREZI: HOW K1ND OF YOU TO JO1N US DOOM3D D34D 3R1D4N!
                
                @terezi_talk TEREZI: 1 4M RUNN1NG SHORT ON M3MB3RS OF TH3 JURY, 4ND 4T TH3 R4T3 W3 4R3 GO1NG W3 4R3 1N D4NG3R OF N3V3R C4TCH1NG D3T3CT1V3 DULC3’S MURD3R3R!
                
                @terezi_talk TEREZI: 1 4M 4FR41D TH4T 1 W1LL SOON N33D TO BYP4SS TH3 CURR3NT D1SCUSS1ON 1N ORD3R TO D1SP3NS3 SOM3...
                
                @terezi_laugh TEREZI: H34V13R 1NT3RROG4T1ON M3THODS!
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: despite this afterlife thing bein a wwhole eternity-long deal
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: i dont havve time for your outlandish make-believe court dramas
                
                @eridan_talk ERIDAN: hey kar while they’re busy RPing and stuff how about I show you around my planet
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: i remember most of the cool parts so it should all be here
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: maybe wwe could finally catch up for real
                
                @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS A LOT MORE EXCITING THAN LISTENING TO FAKE JUDICIAL BABBLE...
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 4M GROW1NG QU1T3 1MP4T13NT 4ND 4NGRY!
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 4M W4RN1NG YOU, DO NOT CROSS TH3 COURTBLOCK MR THR3SH3CUT1ON3R!
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: REALLY, TEREZI, YOU KEPT ANNOYING DAVE AND I INTO COMING UP HERE TODAY, AND THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST LACKLUSTER INCENTIVES YOU COULD HAVE GIVEN US TO DO SO.
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: AND SERIOUSLY, WE’RE NOT EVEN IN A COURT, WE’RE IN THE LAND OF WRATH AND ANGELS.
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: EXCEPT WE’RE NOT EVEN IN THE LAND OF WRATH AND ANGELS WE’RE ON THE FUCKING ROOF OF A BUILDING ON THIS FUCK FORSAKEN ASTEROID.
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: YOU COULD TRY TO CONSIDER THAT POSSIBLY I’D LIKE TO TALK TO A NON-HOMOCIDAL AND NON-SHITHIVE MAGGOTS VERSION OF ONE OF MY OLD FRIENDS INSTEAD OF CATERING TO YOUR FUCKED UP JUDGEMURDER ROLEPLAY NEEDS?
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: >:/
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: YOU KNOW WH4T?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 4T TH1S PO1NT YOU C4N 4LL DO WH4T3V3R TH3 FUCK YOU W4NT
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: ARE YOU SERIOUSLY MAD THAT WE DIDN’T WANT TO BE FORCED INTO ROLEPLAYING?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT DID YOU EVEN WANT TO DO THIS FOR?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: WHY SHOULD YOU C4R3?
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WELL IF YOU WANTED TO DO SOMETHING YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST PLANNED IT BETTER.
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: OR GIVEN US NOTICE.
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WE’RE NOT REALLY THE FUCKING ECCENTRIC ROLEPLAYING TYPE LIKE YOU ARE.
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: WH4T3V3R
                
                @karkat_what KARKAT: ...
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: WELL SORRY.
                
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: you tell her kar
                @eridan_madtalk ERIDAN: don’t let some blind psychopath and her pretend games get betwween us
                
                @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: ERIDAN OF THE AMOUNT OF WORD COMBINATIONS YOU COULD FORCE OUT OF YOUR CHITINOUS WINDTUBE THAT WAS POSSIBLY THE WORST POSSIBLE THING.
                
                @eridan_huh ERIDAN: wwhat
                @eridan_fingers ERIDAN: i just meant-
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: AND WHAT DO YOU MEAN, BETWEEN US?
                
                @karkat_talk KARKAT: DUDE, WE WERE NEVER EVEN _THAT_ CLOSE, OK?
                
                @karkat_yell KARKAT: I DON’T WANT TO GET INTO A FUCKING SPLIT DIMENSION ANTICONFESSION EMOTIONAL BULLSHITCIRCUS, SO CAN YOU JUST NOT SOUND SO STRANGELY ATTATCHED FOR ONCE?
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: ESPECIALY IN FRONT OF OTHER PEOPLE?
                
                @dave_concern DAVE: what the fuck is even happening over there
                @dave_huhtalk DAVE: of all the awkward things thats happened on this asteroid
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: CAN YOU BLUBBERING COCKHEADS JUST CAN IT FOR A SECOND? I’M TRYING TO GET A MESSAGE ACROSS HERE!
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: K4RK4T 1 R3GR3T TO 1NFORM YOU TH4T TH3 ONLY “BLUBB3R1NG COCKH34D” 1N TH3 1MM3D14T3 V1C1N1TY 1S YOU
                
                @karkat_shout KARKAT: SWEET SLUDGESPEWING FUCK WHY AM I THE FUCKING BAD GUY HERE?
                
                @terezi_madtalk TEREZI: 1 DON’T KNOW BUT S1NC3 4PP4R3NTLY 1’M NOT 1NT3R3ST1NG 3NOUGH, 1 TH1NK 1’LL JUST GO.
                
                @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: TEREZI, COME ON...
                
                @terezi_mad TEREZI: NO
            </args>
            <action command='removeSprite'>
                <args>terezi,lowaa</args>
            </action>
        </action>

    </classes>
    
    <assets>
        
        <asset name='tereziSheet' type='graphic'>chars/terezi/terezi.png</asset>
        
        <asset name='terezi_huh' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_huh.png</asset>
        <asset name='terezi_idle' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_idle.png</asset>
        <asset name='terezi_laugh' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_laugh.png</asset>
        <asset name='terezi_mad' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_mad.png</asset>
        <asset name='terezi_madtalk' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_madtalk.png</asset>
        <asset name='terezi_talk' type='graphic'>dialogs/terezi/terezi_talk.png</asset>

    </assets>
    
    <hud>
        <dialogsprites>
			<animation name='terezi_huh' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_huh' />
			<animation name='terezi_idle' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_idle' />
			<animation name='terezi_laugh' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_laugh'  length='2'/>
            <animation name='terezi_mad' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_mad' />
			<animation name='terezi_madtalk' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_madtalk' length='2'/>
			<animation name='terezi_talk' class='terezi-dialog' sheet='terezi_talk' length='2'/>

        </dialogsprites>
    </hud>
</sburb>